

Nguyễn Hoàng Vương

Frontend developer

Date of birth: April 12, 2000

Gender: Male

Phone: 0347689482

Email: hoangvuong1225@gmail.com

Address: 41/58A Cau Xay, Tan Phu Ward, District 9, HCMC

Website: https://www.facebook.com/vuongml0123/

OBJECTIVE

Short-term goal: When being accepted into the position of Frontend developer, the first and short-term goal is to apply the experience and skills to successfully do the job of the Frontend developer position.Long-term goal: In the period from 1 year to 4 years will achieve higher positions in the work and create well-rounded, beneficial products to help the company grow.

EDUCATION

August 2018 - Present University of Transport and Communications campus in HCMC

Major: Information Technology

GPA: 3.5/4 (Studying in 4th year at school)

WORK EXPERIENCE

03/07/2021 - 3/11/2021 Company Mevivu

Frontend Developer

Frontend programming and working on Wordpress

7/03/2022 - nay **FPT Software**

Frontend Developer

Frontend programming ReactJS

ACTIVITIES

2020 - 2021 Participate in scientific research (Check for plagiarism)

Member of Team

Help the team design the interface and handle the basic logic

SKILLS

Language	English basic
----------	---------------

Computer Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Programming skills Proficient in using HTML, CSS and basic knowledge of JS, basic

knowledge of ReactJS, Bootstrap, SASS, PHP, Database and basic of

HTML5, CSS3

INTERESTS

I like soccer, participating in outdoor activities, writing web, traveling

PROJECTS

SPA MANAGER

(2020 - 2021)

Customer	NO
Description	 Website to manage spa bookings with product sales, general information management Link: https://hovuotsax12.000webhostapp.com/spa/
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	All
Technologies used	HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, MySQL, Ajax, PHP

MOVIE WEBSITE

(2020 - 2021)

Customer	NO
Description	- Website to watch movies, search for movies - Link: https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/movie-react/
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	All
Technologies used	ReactJS, HTML, SASS, JS

WORDPRESS PROJECTS

(2020 - 2021)

Customer	Customer 1: Kimmie, Customer 2: Sang
Description	Create a website according to customer requirementsLink:+ Customer 1: https://kimmiebeauty.com/+ Customer 2: http://familyshopping.vn/
Team size	3
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design - Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	HTML, CSS, JS, PHP

CLONE PROJECTS, CUT FIGMA, CUT PSD

(2019 - 2021)

Customer	NO
Description	- Clone web and cut html from the available interface - Link: + https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/LanderLab/ + https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/SetSail/

	+ https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/PSD-Landingpage/ + https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/FECompany1/ + https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/figma1/ + https://nguyenhoangvuong.github.io/figma2/
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	All
Technologies used	ReactJS, HTML, CSS, SASS, JS